Guide to the Nasher Museum of Art records, 1947-2018, bulk 1990s-2018 UA.07.10.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Nasher Museum of Art Records
1947-2018, bulk 1990s-2018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Nasher Museum of Art at Duke University
UA.07.10.0002
20.0 Linear Feet
The Nasher Museum, founded as the Duke University Museum of Art in 1969, opened in its current building in 2005. The museum's collection focuses on works by diverse artists, European medieval art, European and American paintings, Outsider art, classical antiquities, African art, and ancient American art. The Nasher Museum of Art records include materials related to exhibits and events at the Nasher as well as the planning, construction, and opening of the museum building.
Arrangement
Materials have been arranged by accession. Materials have been consolidated into fewer boxes but have not otherwise been arranged. Folder and item titles are largely original.
Biographical / Historical
The Nasher Museum was founded as the Duke University Museum of Art in 1969, in a renovated science building on the University's East Campus. In 1998, Duke alumnus Raymond D. Nasher donated funds to support construction of a new art museum, and it was subsequently named for him. Construction began in 2000 on the new building, designed by Rafael Violy, and the Nasher Museum opened officially in 2005.
The museum's permanent collection focuses on works by diverse artists, particularly artists of African descent, as well as European medieval art, European and American paintings, Outsider art, classical antiquities, African art, and ancient American art. The Nasher also presents rotating exhibitions that frequently travel around the United States and internationally. Major traveling exhibitions have included El Greco to Velázquez: Art during the Reign of Philip III (named one of Time magazine's top 10 shows of 2008) and Southern Accent: Seeking the American South in Contemporary Art (2016-17).
The Director of the Nasher when it opened in 2005 was Kimberly Rorschach, who served in that role from 2004 to 2012. Sarah Schroth served as Interim Director 2012-2013 before serving as Director 2012-2020. Trevor Schoonmaker took over as Director in summer 2020.
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist. Contact Research Services for more information.
Provenance
The Nasher Museum of Art records were received by the Duke University Archives as a series of transfers in 2019 and 2020.
Related Materials
Duke Museum of Art records, UA.07.10.0001, Duke University Archives.
Nasher10, Duke University Archives.
Collection Overview
The Nasher Museum of Art records include materials related to exhibits and events at the Nasher as well as the planning, construction, and opening of the museum building. Included are brochures, programs, clippings and publications, photographs, event planning materials, newsletters, correspondence, and other materials.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Collection contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic/electronic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Art museums -- North Carolina -- Durham; Museum exhibits; Nasher Museum of Art at Duke University; Rorschach, Kimerly
- Accession UA2019.0016
  - DUMA Dinner Party (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure, Fall 1992 (Box 1)
  - Duma Holocaust Exhibition Brochure, 1992 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure Exhibitions and Events, Summer 1994 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure Intro to the Collections (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure Museum Rental Program (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure, Spring - Summer 1992 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Special Collections Department Brochure (Box 1)
  - DUMA Exhibitions and Events Brochure, 1993 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Ph.D. Program in the History of Art Brochure (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure, 1989 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure, 1991 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure, 1991 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Calendar Brochure, 1988 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure, 1990 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Brochure, 1990 (Box 1)
  - DUMA The Brummer Founders Event Invite, 2001 (Box 1)
  - DUMA 25th Anniversary Dinner Invite, 1994 (Box 1)
  - DUMA 20th Century Bolivian Textiles Brochure, 1987 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Gala Dinner, 1996 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Newsletter, Spring 2000 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Museum Book, 8 folders (Box 1)
  - DUMA Staircase Photograph (Box 1)
  - DUMA Staircase Under Construction/ Finished Photograph (Box 1)
  - DUMA Gallery Photograph (Box 1)
  - DUMA Exhibition Photograph (Box 1)
  - Daily Dialogue, May 7, 2002 (Box 1)
  - The Chronicle, November 5, 1991 (Box 1)
  - The News and Observer, June 6, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Article about DUMA, June 10, 1988 (Box 1)
  - The DUMA Newsletter, Fall 1988 (Box 1)
  - The News and Observer, April 17, 1988 (Box 1)
  - The News and Observer, December 7, 1994 (Box 1)
  - The Herald Sun, December 23, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Art + Tech at DUMA, April 8, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Leisure, 1989 September 03 (Box 1)
  - The Chronicle, November 4, 1994 (Box 1)
  - The Herald Sun, October 6, 1996 (Box 1)
  - The Chronicle, March 26, 1998 (Box 1)
  - The Chronicle, March 25, 1998 (Box 1)
  - DUMA in the North Carolina Beacon, December 23, 1993 (Box 1)
  - DUMA in the Herald Sun, December 9, 1994 (Box 1)
  - DUMA in the Paper (Box 1)
  - DUMA in the Dialogue, November 18, 1994 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Film for Pictures (Box 1)
  - Construction Plans Building Program, January 16, 2001 (Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Administrative restriction until 2026.
  - Construction Plans Nasher Basement Floor Plan, circa 2001 (Box 1)
  - Construction Plans Nasher Building, circa 2001 (Box 1)
  - Nasher Construction Plans General Notes, January 16, 2001 (Box 1)
  - The Herald Sun, January 20, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Front Page (Box 1)
  - New York Times, November 13, 1998 (Box 1)
  - VP Alum Dev, April 13, 1999 (Box 1)
  - The Chronicle, November 16, 1998 (Box 1)
  - The News and Observer, March 5, 2005 (Box 1)
  - The Herald Sun, 2005 March 05 (Box 1)
  - Upcoming Exhibitions Schedule, March 4, 2006 - July 16, 2006 (Box 1)
  - The new Nasher at Duke to end the fall with the evolution of the Nasher Collection, October 2, 2005 (Box 1)
  - The New Nasher at Duke will present the forest: Politics, Poetics, and Practice, October 2, 2005 (Box 1)
  - The Herald Sun, July 9, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Towerview, October 2005 (Box 1)
  - The News and Observer, October 19, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Friends Website, Spring - Summer 2004 (Box 1)
  - Friends Events (Box 1)
  - Inside Nasher Beam (Box 1)
  - Save the date for Nasher Opening, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Duke News and Communications, Dec. 2, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Duke News and Communications, May 16, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Duke News and Communications, Dec. 6, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Duke News and Communications, October 2, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Duke Dialogue, 2001-02-16T00:00:00+00:00 (Box 1)
  - Duke Dialogue, May 19, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Duke Dialogue, March 10, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Metro Magazine, March 2003 (Box 1)
  - For Immediate Release, Nov. 1998 (Box 1)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 2004 January 16 (Box 1)
  - News and Observer, 2003 December 04 (Box 1)
  - Exhibition Schedule, 2005-2008 (Box 1)
  - History of the Nasher Museum at Duke University, circa 2000s (Box 1)
    Adminsitrative restriction until 2030.
  - Nasher Museum Skylight Mockup Pictures, 2002 November 13 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2027.
  - Nasher Logo Ideas, circa 2001-2005 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2030.
  - Visitor Comment Cards, 2006 June 29 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2031.
  - PR clips on Russian conceptual art of the 1980s (Box 1)
  - Michael Mezzatesta in the Herald, 1993 November 29 (Box 1)
  - Resnicow Schroeder PR comments on new museum, 2004 February 09 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2029.
  - Thank you letter to new Brummer members, circa 2004-2005 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Wendy from Jerry, 2005 March 22 (Box 1)
  - Chicago Tribune, 2004 April 14 (Box 1)
  - St. Barbara sculpture, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Pictures of the Nasher Building Inside and Outside, 2005 July 25 (Box 1)
  - Nasher Museum Negatives, 2004 November 09 (Box 1)
  - Joseph D. Rowland Photo, 2002 (Box 1)
  - DSA Students Night, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Outside DUMA Building Pictures, circa 2003-2006 (Box 1)
  - Negatives of Random Man, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Kimberly Rorschach photo, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - DUMA Gala, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - DUMA Friends Pictures, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Nasher Groundbreaking Celebration, 2001 December 06 (Box 1)
  - Seman's Gala, circa 2005 (Box 1)
  - Groundbreaking Celebrations 2001 negatives (Box 1)
  - Rafael Vinoly Pictures, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Rafael Vinoly Negatives, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Rafael Vinoly Article, 2000 February 03 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2025.
  - Picture of Mary Duke Biddle, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Sarah Schroth Joining Staff Letter, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Anne Schroeder Assoc. Curator Photo, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Sarah Schroth Photo, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Duke Professor Reynolds Price Photo, circa 2000s (Box 1)
  - Letter from Steve Nash to Joseph Rowland with picture, 1998 December 02 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2023.
  - Photos of Michael Mezzatesta DUMA Director, 2003 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2028.
  - El Greco Gala Photos, 2008 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2033.
  - Family Day Photos, 2009 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2034.
  - Kim Rorschach Photos in Office, 2009 (Box 1)
  - Family Day Photos, November 2008 (Box 1)
  - Family Day, 2008 September 08 (Box 1)
  - Student Party, 2008 September 24 (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher in World Fall Magazine, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher and colleagues visit construction site, December 4, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Invite to a special evening with Ray Nasher, January 29, 1999 (Box 1)
    Administrative restriction until 2024.
  - Raymond Nasher Navy Picture, circa 1940s (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher Tennis Team, 1942 (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher outside zeta Beta tau House, 1940 (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher Zeta Beta Tau, 1942 (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher Zeta Beta Tau, 1943 (Box 1)
  - Letter from the White House about Raymond Nasher, July 1, 1999 (Box 1)
  - DUMA Friends Newsletter, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher Yearbook, 1943 (Box 1)
  - Nasher member invitation letter, October 10, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Nasher staff pictures, 2009 (Box 1)
  - Raymond Nasher in Bostonia Magazine, Spring 2000 (Box 1)
  - Pictures of Ray and Patsy Nasher's Exhibition at the Nasher (Box 1)
  - DUMA Friends Letter Spring 2000 (Box 1)
  - Nasher Construction Plans, January 16, 2001; February 2, 2001 (Box 1)
- Accession UA2019.0029
  - Media Preview Postcard, September 28, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Student Postcard, September 2005 (Box 2)
  - Opening Postcard, October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Patrick Dougherty Postcard, October 2005 (Box 2)
  - The Forest, October 2, 2005 - January 29, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Permanent Collection Exibition Guide (Box 2)
  - Nasher Collection Exibition Guide, October 2, 2005 - May 21, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Grand Opening Press Kit, October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Festival Postcard Opening, October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Side Steppin' (Patrick Dougherty), 2005 - 2006 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newsletter, Fall 2005 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newsletter, Winter 2005 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Rack Card, 2005 - 2006 (Box 2)
  - Grant Hill Press Kit (Box 2)
  - Something All Our Own Exibition Guide, March 4 - July 16, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Something All Our Own Poster, March 4 - July 16, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Community Open House Insert, April 29, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newsletter, Spring 2006 (Box 2)
  - DUMA Docents Handbook, 1998 - 1999 (Box 2)
  - DUMA Docent Handbook, 1999 - 2000 (Box 2)
  - DUMA Docent Handbook, 2002 - 2003 (Box 2)
  - DUMA Docent Handbook, 2003 - 2004 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newletter, Summer 2006 (Box 2)
  - Bearden Press Kit (Box 2)
  - Conjuring Bearden Poster, March 4 - July 16, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Conjuring Bearden Exibition Guide, March 4 - July 16, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newsletter, Fall 2006 (Box 2)
  - Sussman Poster Mailer, October 26, 2006 - Feburary 18, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Memorials of Identity Brochure, August 3 - October 1, 2006 (Box 2)
  - First Annual Report, 2006 (Box 2)
  - China Show Poster Mailer, October 26, 2006 - Feburary 18, 2007 (Box 2)
  - China Show Exibition Guide, October 26, 2006 - Feburary 18, 2007 (Box 2)
  - China Show Postcard, October 26, 2006 - Feburary 18, 2007 (Box 2)
  - School Tour and Teacher Programs, Fall 2006 - Winter 2007 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newletter, Winter 2007 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newsletter, Spring 2007 (Box 2)
  - Krens Lecture Postcard, Feburary 21, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newsletter, Summer 2007 (Box 2)
  - Blake Byrne Exibition Guide, April 19, 2007 - September 30, 2008 (Box 2)
  - School Tour and Teacher Programs, Fall 2007 (Box 2)
  - Taste of the Modern Exibition Guide, October 11, 2007 - September 14, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Street Level Postcard, March 29 - July 29, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Street Level Exibition Guide, March 29 - July 29, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Kremen Postcard, March 22 - June 17, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Kremen Exibition Guide, March 22 - June 17, 2007 (Box 2)
  - From the Root Postcard (Box 2)
  - New at Nasher Exibition Guide, June 19, 2007 - July 6, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newletter, Fall 2007 (Box 2)
  - Kehinde Wiley Postcard, September 15, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Perjovschi Postcards, August 29 - 30, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Perjovschi Exibition Guide, August 23, 2007 - January 6, 2008 (Box 2)
  - New at the Nasher! Postcard, July 18, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Annual Report, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Newletter, Winter 2008 (Box 2)
  - Barkley Hendricks Exibition Guide (Box 2)
  - Barkley Hendricks Postcard, Feburary 7 - July 13, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Barkley Hendricks Mini-guide (Box 2)
  - Barkley Hendricks Table Tent (Box 2)
  - Barkley Hendricks Poster (Box 2)
  - Barkley Hendricks Realted Programs and Events, February 7 - July 13, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Barkley Hendricks Artist Lecture, October 15, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Young Friends Events, Winter/Spring 2008 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Museum Opening Poster, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Nasher Poster (Box 2)
- Accession UA2019.0032
  - Miscellaneous Photos from Nasher Events and History (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Magazines (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Tapes (Box 3)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0002)
    Scope and Contents
    Events documented include 2003 Alumni event in Dallas, the 2005 and 2010 Annual Meeting of the Nasher Museum Friends Board, 2005 Director's Reception, staff going away party, and 2005 Taste of Durham celebration. Digital photographs in JPEG and Adobe PSD formats.
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0006)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0007)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0008)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0009)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0010)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0012)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0013)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0015)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0016)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0017)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0018)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0020)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0022)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0023)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0024)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0025)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0029)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0030)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0031)
  - Event images, 2002-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0034)
  - Exhibit images, 2004-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0002)
    Includes images from the exhibits The Forest: Politics, Poetics, and Practice; The Record: Contemporary Art and Vinyl; Between Past and Future: New Photography and Video from China; and Sacred Beauty: Medieval and Renaissance Illuminated Manuscripts from the Collection of Robert J. Parsons. For the exhibit Beyond Beauty: Photographs from the Duke University Special Collections Library, caption text is included with images. Also included are sculpture installation photographs of works by Mark Di Survero, Anthony Caro, Alain Kirili, and unidentified artists. Also included are photographs from an unidentified exhibit catalogue and unidentified exhibit. Digital images in JPEG and TIFF formats. Document files in MS Word and PowerPoint formats.
  - Exhibit images, 2004-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0005)
  - Exhibit images, 2004-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0028)
  - Exhibit images, 2004-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0032)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0002)
    Photographic portraits of Trevor Schoonmaker, Dave Hickey, and unidentified staff members. Digital images in JPEG format.
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0003)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0005)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0019)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0021)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0026)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0027)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0032)
  - Photographic portraits, 2006-2010 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0039)
  - Pre-Opening images, 2003-2005 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0004)
    Includes images of the Nasher museum during construction and prior to opening, as well as presentations from a pre-opening public presentations. Digital images in JPEG and TIFF formats. Presentation files in MS PowerPoint format.
  - The State of Things with Frank Stasio episode featuring Irwin Kremen, 2007 (Box UA07100002-SET-0001, Optical-disc UA07100002-OP-0032, UA07100002-OP-0033, UA07100002-OP-0035)
    Audio recording of Public Radio broadcast episode featuring Irwin Kremen, promoting his exhibit Beyond Black Mountain, 1966-2006. Recordings in WAV format.
- Accession UA2019.0034
  - Press Clippings, 1990s - 2018 (Box 4)
  - Press Clippings, 1990s - 2018 (Box 5)
- Accession UA2019.0019
  - Nasher Progress Reports, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Semans Lecture Speech, 2012 (Box 6)
    Administrative restriction until 2037.
  - Nasher Construction Documents, circa 2001-2005 (Box 6)
  - Nasher Construction Documents, includes preparations and plans, 2001-2004 (Box 6)
  - Nasher Construction and Design Plans, 2001 (Box 20)
  - Directors Papers: Administrators to Council for the Arts, circa 2000s (Box 7)
  - Directors Papers: Council for the Arts to Wiley Dinner, circa 2000s (Box 8)
  - Nasher Opening Subject Files, includes brochues, events, exhibitions, circa 2005; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - DUMA Files, including Arts Task Force and Internal Audit reports, 1990s (Box 9)
  - Nasher Grand Opening Files, circa 2005 (Box 10)
  - Nasher Collection Policy Review, 2006-2008 (Box 10)
  - Directors Papers: Correspondence, Events, Initiatives, 1990s (Box 10)
  - Directors Papers: Correspondence, Events, Initiatives, 1990s (Box 11)
  - DUMA Publications, 2 items (Box 11)
  - Photographs, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - DUMA Friends Bylaws (Box 11)
    Diskette
  - Blueprints, Asbury, 1947 October 08 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Topographical Surveys, 1980; 5 items (Oversize-folder 1)
  - FMD Campus Map, 1999 March 29 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Art Museum for Duke University, 1967; 5 items (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Architectural Drawings: Alteration to Science Building, 1988 July 30 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Art Museum Renovation (Science/Friedl Building), 1987 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Copies of Horace Trumbauer Drawings, Revised Science Building, 1925 (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Alterations to Science Building, 1968; 2 items (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Topographical Survey Plan (present day Nasher site), 1989 October 13 (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Nasher 100% Construction Documents as Issued (many items), 2002 February 04 (Oversize-folder 3)
- Accession UA2019.0085
  - Budget Files, circa 2000s (Box 19)
  - Annual Reports, circa 2000s (Box 19)
  - Advisory Council Reports, circa 2000s (Box 19)
  - Art of Shopping Catalog (features photographs of Nasher) (Box 20)
- Accession UA2020.0004
  - Gala Event binders, 2008-2011; 2013-2015; 9 folders (Box 19)
    Administrative restriction until 2040.
- Accession UA2020.0014
  - Clippings (Box 12)
  - Clippings (Box 12)
  - Press Clippings: Grand Opening (Box 12)
  - Press Clippings, September 2005 (Box 12)
  - Clips, 2006-2007 (Box 12)
  - Press Clippings, Winter-Spring 2006 (Box 12)
  - Printed Materials, 2005-Spring 2007 (Box 12)
  - Nasher Tear Sheets (Box 12)
    Administrative restriction for 25 years.
  - Untitled Folder (Box 13)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 13)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 13)
  - Print Adverstising (Box 13)
  - Perjovschi Exhibit Clippings (Box 13)
  - El Greco to Velazquez, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 13)
  - El Greco Reading List (Box 13)
  - Barkley L. Hendricks Birth of the Cool Mini-CD, 6 items (Box 14)
    Mini-CD, 6 copies
  - Nasher Opening Panel Discussion, October 2, 2005; 2 items (Box 14)
    DVCAM
  - Nasher Museum Panel Discussion, September 27, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Nasher INT/B-Roll, September 27, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Grant Hill (Box 14)
    VHS
  - UNC-TV, May 1, 2006 (Box 14)
  - UNC-TV: Kimerly Rorschach, October 28, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Welcome to Durham Documentary Soundtrack, 2007 (Box 14)
    Administrative restriction until 2032.
    CD/DVD, 3rd party
  - Time Cosmique by Lyota Yagi, 2008 (Box 14)
    DVD, 3rd party
  - Seman Lecture: Powerpoint and Images (Box 14)
    DVD
  - Jason Rubell (Rubell Family Collection) Powerpoint (Box 14)
  - Lecture: Architecture/Media in Film Editing (Box 14)
  - Mary D.B.T. Semans Interview with WUNC-TV, April 2, 2003 (Box 14)
  - "The Art of Architecture and the Architecture of Art", 2005 (Box 14)
  - Local News Broadcasts of Grand Opening, September 28, 2005; October 2, 2005; 2 items (Box 14)
    DVD, 2 copies
  - President Broadhead Poetry, January 31, 2006 (Box 14)
  - George Rousse Lecture, September 13, 2006 (Box 14)
  - "The Past is Present: Classical Antiquities at the Nasher Museum, March 21, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Street Level, March 29, 2007 (Box 14)